<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Entota Help on Entota Hugo POC</title>
    <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Entota Help on Entota Hugo POC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Relationship to a Non-Strategy Asset</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addarelationshiptoanonstrategyasset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addarelationshiptoanonstrategyasset/</guid>
      <description>Non-Strategy assets include terms, rules, policies, data sets and systems.
To add a relationship to a non-strategy asset:
  On the asset detail page, click a tab for an asset relationship.
  If there are no existing related assets, click the Setting Relationships button.
  If there are existing related assets, click the Edit () icon; the Relate Asset sidebar displays.
  Begin typing an asset name in the text field and click the asset link when it appears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Sponsor to an Asset</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/add_a_sponsor_to_an_asset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/add_a_sponsor_to_an_asset/</guid>
      <description>You can add one or more sponsors to your asset. When you add or remove a sponsor, the sponsor receives a notification in their notification panel and email, depending on their user settings.
To add or remove a sponsor:
  Click the Sponsors icon () on an asset&amp;rsquo;s detail page.
  Do one of the following:
  In the Sponsors selection panel, scroll to and click a person&amp;rsquo;s name to select that person as a sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up a System</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/set_up_a_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/set_up_a_system/</guid>
      <description>Systems allow a user to capture information about where data is stored, whether it is in a flat file, an ERP system, a database, a data warehouse or other locations.
As you are setting up a System, you can click the Guidance ( ) icon to open the Guidance panel to view assistance. Refer to [Guidance] ( https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/guidance/guidance/) for more information.
To add a System:
  Click the plus sign (Add) icon on the Home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Terms</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_terms/</guid>
      <description>You can define terms to improve business understanding and use of data.
As you are setting up a term, you can click the Guidance () icon to open the Guidance panel to view assistance. Refer to Guidance for more information.
NOTE: If a user does not have permission to add an asset, it displays dimmed with a lock icon on the Quick Add menu.
To add a term:
  Click the plus sign (Add) icon on the Home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share URLs for Assets</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/share_urls_for_assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/share_urls_for_assets/</guid>
      <description>You can collaborate with other users by sharing the URL for an asset.
To copy the asset&amp;rsquo;s direct link to share:
 Search for the asset. In the asset&amp;rsquo;s Preview panel, click the Copy direct link to clipboard () icon.  This copies the link to your clipboard. Next, you can paste the link to share, for example in an email.
To share the URL for an asset from the asset&amp;rsquo;s details page:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Relationship to a Strategy Asset</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addarelationshiptoastrategyasset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addarelationshiptoastrategyasset/</guid>
      <description>When working in Strategy, you can only create asset relationships for goals and initiatives, and only to other goals and initiatives. Relationships to other assets (Rules, Policies, Terms, Systems, Data Sets) must be created on those detail pages using the asset relationship tabs. Refer to Add a Relationship to a Non-Strategy Asset for more information.
Goals-to-goal and initiative-to-initiative relationships can only be added by rolling the program-level asset up to the company-level asset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/migration_dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/migration_dashboard/</guid>
      <description>The Migration dashboard, available with DSP 7.0.1 and later, provides visibility into progress and status associated with enterprise Data Migration efforts by giving you access to the most important migration project metrics.
Using this dashboard you can:
 Understand the current status of migration waves Identify any waves that are running behind schedule Ascertain go-live readiness for a wave  Whether you are responsible for one or multiple waves, across a single instance or multiple instances in the DSP, you can view progress against milestones to assess risk, determine a need for resource adjustment and communicate effectively to all project stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Admin</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/search_admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/search_admin/</guid>
      <description>You can search for a user account in Admin. You can only search within First Name or Last Name. Operators (for example, AND, OR, NOT or AND NOT) and wildcard characters (for example, &amp;ldquo;*&amp;ldquo;or &amp;ldquo;?&amp;quot;) are not allowed in the search.
You can search by partial words. For example, a search for &amp;ldquo;Jo&amp;rdquo; would return Joe, John and Joseph.
To search in Admin:
 Enter your search criteria in the search bar and then click the Search icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up a Data Set</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/set_up_a_data_set/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/set_up_a_data_set/</guid>
      <description>Data Sets can be a subset of a single System or span Systems and tie the generic business-focused documentation of terms, policies and rules to where the data is stored. For example, a rule can score the Data Set for data quality. A term can be related to Data Sets, which also ties the term to their related Systems. A business process could create a Data Set.
NOTE: If a user does not have permission to add an asset, it displays dimmed with a lock icon on the Quick Add menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Policies</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_policies/</guid>
      <description>You can add policy to your strategy. Polices are a statement of a standard that guides business decisions. You can define the policy and provide the purpose of the policy, in other words the business reason this policy has been implemented.
Policies are enforced by Rules.
As you are setting up a policy, you can click the Guidance () icon to open the Guidance panel to view assistance. Refer to Guidance for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor an Asset</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/sponsor_an_asset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/sponsor_an_asset/</guid>
      <description>As a sponsor of an asset, you can update the status of the asset and provide endorsement of or contest an asset.
When the asset details are defined, sponsors are notified and a sponsor moves the asset to Review status and all sponsors of the asset are notified. If a sponsor contests an asset that is in Review status, the asset is moved back to Candidate status and the color of the Status text changes to reflect that it has been contested, and all sponsors and assignees will receive notification by email, depending on their user settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Change History for Assets</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/view_change_history_for_assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/view_change_history_for_assets/</guid>
      <description>You can view changes to an asset including the name of the person who changed the asset along with the date and time of the change. You can view the details for the change to see:
 Location &amp;ndash; The name of field that changed Previous &amp;ndash; The contents of the field before it was changed New &amp;ndash; The new contents of the field  To view the change history for an asset:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision, Mission, Goals, and Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/vision_mission_goals_and_initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/vision_mission_goals_and_initiatives/</guid>
      <description>You can define the strategy for accomplishing your business objective by adding Vision, Mission, Goals, and Initiatives to the strategy. You can add Vison, Mission, Goals and Initiatives at a company and program strategy level.
Learn about Vision, Mission, Goals, and Initiatives:
 Add a Vision Add a Mission Add Goals Add Initiatives  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Term-to-Term Relationship</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addatermtotermrelationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/addatermtotermrelationship/</guid>
      <description>The following types of term-to-term relationships can be added on the Terms tab of a term detail page:
NOTE: For example, you can add &amp;ldquo;is related to&amp;rdquo; relationships between the term Customer to terms such as Name, Phone Number, Address, and Telephone Number. Alternatively, you can add an &amp;ldquo;is part of a(n)&amp;rdquo; relationship between Customer and Address, as an Address is part of a customer record. You can also establish a relationship where Customer &amp;quot;has a(n)&amp;quot; Sales Order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a User to Entota</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/add_a_user_to_entota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/add_a_user_to_entota/</guid>
      <description>You can add a user to Entota™ and assign permissions.
You can grant a combination of the following permissions to a user depending on the access required.
 ADMIN - Can add and edit user accounts and set user permissions to Platform components. APPROVER - Can be set as an Owner for elements and can approve elements in order to publish them. AUTHOR - Can create child elements - Processes, Scenarios, Roles, Tasks, and assets such as Terms, Rules, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Vision</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_a_vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_a_vision/</guid>
      <description>A Vision is the result that is accomplished by the Strategy.
To add a vision:
 Select the Strategy to which you are adding the Vision from the Strategy drop-down. Click the Vision tab. Click the Click Here To Get Started link. Enter the vision Statement. Enter a detailed Description of the Vision. Click Save.  To edit a Vision, click the Vision tab on the home page, and then click the Pencil () icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment on an Asset</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/comment_on_an_asset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/comment_on_an_asset/</guid>
      <description>You can comment on assets. Commenting, unless you are commenting about a Contest to an asset, does not change the status of the asset. You can include URL links in your comments.
To comment on an asset:
  Search for and open the asset.
  Enter the comment in the Add a New Comment field in the comments panel.
  Click the plus () icon.
NOTE: To edit or delete your comment after it has been added, you can click the pencil or X icon next to the comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contest an Asset (Non-sponsors)</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/contest_an_asset_non-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/sponsors/contest_an_asset_non-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>You can contest an asset whether or not you are a sponsor of the asset. If an Accepted asset is contested, it is moved back to Candidate status and must be re-endorsed by the asset&#39;s sponsors. All Sponsors and Assignees are notified by email, depending on their user settings, when the asset is contested. Refer to Sponsor an Asset for more information.
To contest an asset:
  Click the drop-down menu for the asset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/director_dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/director_dashboard/</guid>
      <description>You can view a dashboard with Entota™ centric metrics and information. You must have permissions to the Director persona in Admin to access the dashboard. Refer to Add a User for more information. Once you have Persona set to Director, the dashboard is displayed as soon as you log in.
NOTE: The dashboard is generally updated once daily, but can be updated more frequently. Refer to the date and time stamp in the upper right corner of the dashboard to see when it was last updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Rules</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/terms-policies-and-rules/set_up_rules/</guid>
      <description>Business Rules can define controls for business data to help businesses achieve goals. Rule compliance is assessed based on a true or false analysis. If the rule statement is true, the rule is achieved. If the statement is false, it is not achieved.
Rules are assigned to Policies.
As you are setting up a rule, you can click the Guidance () icon to open the Guidance panel to view assistance. Refer to Guidance for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Mission</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_a_mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_a_mission/</guid>
      <description>A Mission is a purpose statement for accomplishing the Vision.
To add a Mission:
 Select the Strategy to which you are adding the Mission from the Strategy drop-down. Click the Mission tab. Click the Click Here To Get Started link. Enter the mission Statement. Enter a detailed Description of the Mission. Click Save.  To edit a Mission, click the Mission tab on the home page and then click the Pencil () icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Supporting Documentation to Assets</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/add_supporting_doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/add_supporting_doc/</guid>
      <description>You can attach documentation that relates to an asset.
To add supporting documentation to an asset:
  Search for and open the asset.
  Click the Supporting Documentation tab.
  Add the title for the documentation in the ADD TITLE field.
  Paste the URL to the documentation in the PASTE URL field.
NOTE: Starting with DSP 7.0.2, users can easily copy DSP page URLs, filtered or with binding criteria, to use as documentation for an asset in Entota.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Guidance™ Inferred Relationships</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/deep_guidance_inferred_relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/relationships/deep_guidance_inferred_relationships/</guid>
      <description>Entota™ can infer a relationship between assets using Deep Guidance™, which examines the language used in describing an asset to determine a relationship. For example, Deep Guidance™ analyzes the Definition of a Term for language that has previously been used in a Rule to create an inferred relationship between the two. The inferred relationship is automatically associated on the detail page for both the Term and Rule.
The Discover icon in the Relate Assets pane on a detail page indicates assets that are related using Deep Guidance™.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director Dashboard Deep Guidance</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/director_dashboard_deep_guidancd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/dashboards/director_dashboard_deep_guidancd/</guid>
      <description>When you are viewing the dashboard, you can click the Guidance () icon to view assets for which you have responsibility.
NOTE: You must have the Director Persona set in your user account in Admin to view the dashboard.
On the Entota™ landing page, you can click the Guidance icon to view:
 Assets assigned to you Assets recently endorsed across all users Assets you are sponsoring  You can hover over an asset in the list to see the full description.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edit a User Account</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/edit_a_user_account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/edit_a_user_account/</guid>
      <description>You can edit a user account if you have been granted Admin level permission in the Platform component.
To edit a user account:
  Click the Applications icon.
  Click the Administration icon in the options panel.
  Click the edit icon on the user account card.
  Update Locale.
NOTE: Or, leave en (English) as the default. The Locale sets the date format for Entota™.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Import Fields to a System</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/import_fields_to_a_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data-catalog/import_fields_to_a_system/</guid>
      <description>You can upload field metadata for a System in a zipped JSON file using the upload option on the System detail page.
Fields JSON Import File Format Use the following schema information to format the JSON file that is used to load field metadata for a System.
Format:
{
&amp;quot;version&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;2018-02-07&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;fields&amp;quot;:[
{
&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;...&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;location&amp;quot;: {...},
&amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: {..}
}
]
}
 You can request a sample JSON file by submitting a request to support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Goals</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_goals/</guid>
      <description>A Goal is a time bound and measurable achievement that is directly tied to and supports the accomplishment of a Mission.
You can add a company or program level goal. You can roll a program level goal up to a company level goal. All associated program level goals are displayed on company level goals.
Before you begin this task, make sure you have selected the correct context from the Company and Program strategy level drop-down on the Home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enforcement Profiles</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/enforcementprofiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/asset-options/enforcementprofiles/</guid>
      <description>Enforcement Profiles document information about the purpose, the implementation, and the technology behind rule enforcement. With this information, business and technical users can easily understand how rules are enforced and the impact rules have on the business. The profiles accommodate different types of rules: rules that are automatically enforced via enforcement technology (for example, the DSP®), rules that are enforced via manual tasks, and rules that are not enforced but require documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update My Profile</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/update_my_profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/update_my_profile/</guid>
      <description>Once your account has been added by an administrator, you can update your profile to change Locale, which controls how dates are formatted.
In addition, you can opt in or opt out of the Optional Information tracking as described in the BackOffice Associates Privacy Policy. Only the user to which the account applies can change this setting. Administrators cannot update this setting for users. You can access the policy at any time by clicking the Privacy Policy link in the Entota™ footer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/strategy/add_initiatives/</guid>
      <description>An Initiative defines the plan for how the Goals are going to be achieved. Initiatives are time bound and their achievement is measurable.
You can add a company or program level initiative. You can roll a program level initiative up to a company level initiative. All associated program level initiatives are displayed on company level initiatives.
Before you begin this task, make sure you have selected the correct context from the Company and Program strategy level drop-down on the Home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entota WebSocket Firewall Requirements</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/entota_websocket_firewall_requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/administration/entota_websocket_firewall_requirements/</guid>
      <description>Entota uses the WebSocket protocol for a few different features, mainly centered around the deep guidance module. The WebSocket protocol has some required HTTP headers that aren&amp;rsquo;t commonly used and tend to be stripped out by corporate firewall software. Below is an example of a BOA app client initiated WebSocket request to BOA cloud, and the response back to the client. All of the headers outlined in this example are required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/add_a_category/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/add_a_category/</guid>
      <description>Add a Category In the Process Designer, a Category allows you to organize your Processes and their elements into logical groupings, such as line of business, business unit, data domain, etc.
  Click + to add a Category.
  Enter a Category Name.
NOTE: The name must be unique.
  Select Owner(s).
NOTE: Owners must have Approver access for the Process Designer component and the Category in use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/add_a_process_or_scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/add_a_process_or_scenario/</guid>
      <description>Add a Process or Scenario Process Designer is the application that enables you to visually build and manage your processes. You can access the detail modal to add a Process or Scenario element. Adding a Process or Scenario element is the first step in creating an Information Governance flow.
  In the Process Designer, select a Category to begin.
  Click an Add New card to add a Process or Scenario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/categories/</guid>
      <description>Categories You can access the detail modal to add a Category.
Entota™ allows you to create categories to organize Processes and their elements into logical groupings, such as line of business, business unit, data domain, etc. Access to the features presented in the tour depends on your user permissions.
To use Categories:
 Add a Category  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/contact_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/contact_support/</guid>
      <description>Contact Support If you have questions or want to report an issue, our support team is available to help. You can open a ticket (after self-registration) on our support site at https://support.boaweb.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/contribute_to_product_ideas_portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/contribute_to_product_ideas_portal/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to Product Ideas Portal Do you have suggestions to improve BackOffice Associates products? Want to see what other users have submitted? Visit the BackOffice Ideas Portal, where Product Managers review all ideas and provide feedback about whether they will be included in an upcoming release. If the feature you suggest is released, you will even receive an email.
Once you sign in to the Ideas Portal, you can:
 Submit an idea View all submitted ideas, including the review status, any conversations attached to the idea, and other details Use filters to view ideas by product and review status Vote on ideas you would like to see implemented   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data_insiders_community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/data_insiders_community/</guid>
      <description>Data Insiders Community Data Insiders is a community of data experts that facilitates the sharing of knowledge. The community fosters collaboration to help our customers be successful using our products and services. Join the Data Insiders community to collaborate with other data experts.
Data Insiders have the opportunity to converse directly with each other and BackOffice Associates® development and services teams to learn how to leverage the features available in the Data Stewardship Platform® and the Entota™ (Entota™)™.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/edit_a_process_or_scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/edit_a_process_or_scenario/</guid>
      <description>Edit a Process or Scenario   Click the Process Designer icon.
  Click the Edit icon.
NOTE: The edit icon looks like this:   Click the dot under each label to navigate to different tabs.
NOTE: The colored dot represents the current tab location.
  Update information as needed, then click Save.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/ideas_portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/ideas_portal/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to Product Ideas Portal Do you have suggestions to improve BackOffice Associates products? Want to see what other users have submitted? Visit the BackOffice Ideas Portal, where Product Managers review all ideas and provide feedback about whether they will be included in an upcoming release. If the feature you suggest is released, you will even receive an email.
Once you sign in to the Ideas Portal, you can:
 Submit an idea View all submitted ideas, including the review status, any conversations attached to the idea, and other details Use filters to view ideas by product and review status Vote on ideas you would like to see implemented  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/basic_navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/basic_navigation/</guid>
      <description>Basic Navigation Access Online Help To access online help, click the Help link in the site&amp;rsquo;s footer. Once the online help opens, a Welcome topic displays. To return to this page at any time in your session, click the Entota™ logo in the top left corner of the page.
Navigate Help To find a specific topic, use the search bar, otherwise topics that describe tasks that the user performs or that the product performs display in a right side menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/online_help_search_tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/online_help_search_tips/</guid>
      <description>Online Help Search Tips To search help, enter a search term, and click the Search icon, which is the magnifying glass on the Page toolbar.
The search results display. The matching results show how many times the term is mentioned. A link to each of the topics containing the search term displays.
Use quotes around multiple word search terms (for example, &amp;ldquo;data source&amp;rdquo;) to view the topics that contain the exact phrase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/print_feedback_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/use-help/print_feedback_version/</guid>
      <description>Print, Remove Highlights, Footer Links and Feedback Print To print a topic, click the Print icon on the toolbar.
Remove Highlights Click the Remove Highlights button next to the Print icon on the toolbar to remove highlighted search words from a topic&#39;s text.
Footer Links The following elements are available in the footer of every topic:
 Links to BackOffice&#39;s Terms of Use, Trademarks and Privacy Policy Links to Contact Support, Access the Product Ideas Portal and Request Product Training A link to the Knowledge Base  Feedback Use the feedback buttons at the bottom of each topic to send feedback about the online help content for the current topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0418/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0418/</guid>
      <description>April 2018 April 30, 2018 Bug Fix [IGC-351] - Fixed an issue that caused multiple errors when adding tasks to a published scenario by updating the status of that scenario when changes to roles and tasks are made.
April 26, 2018 Bug Fixes  [IGC-1178] – Fixed an issue where the horizontal dividing lines in the left panel on asset detail pages were missing. [IGC-1179] – Fixed an issue where suggested terms in all caps were not being truncated in the guidance panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0818/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0818/</guid>
      <description>August 2018 August 30, 2018 Enhancement You can view a dashboard with Entota™ centric metrics and information. You must have permissions to the Director persona in Admin to access the dashboard. Refer to Entota™ Dashboard for more information.
Bug Fix [IGC-1495] — Fixed an issue where when a user navigated away from an asset page without making changes, the user was prompted to save.
August 24, 2018 Enhancement [IGC-1351] — Removed redundant feature flag gates that inhibited persona-based dashboard from displaying for all tenants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2017</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1217/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1217/</guid>
      <description>December 2017 December 18, 2017 Various fixes and minor improvements.
December 11, 2017 Various fixes and minor improvements.
December 04, 2017  Get governance programs up and running quickly through Deep Guidance™ infused with expertise and best practices that focuses teams on creating the highest value assets for governance. Achieve effective governance of data as defined by business users who have the best insights on business strategy versus technology driven approaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1218/</guid>
      <description>December 2018 December 20, 2018 Enhancements  Starting with DSP 7.0.2, users can now easily copy DSP page URLs, filtered or with binding criteria, to use as documentation for an asset in IGC. These URLs are copied from any page in the DSP by using the Copy URL to Clipboard option in the DSP Settings menu. The URL takes them to the page where it was generated with the same drill through and the same filters applied, so users can target specific records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0218/</guid>
      <description>February 2018 February 22, 2018 Bug Fixes  [IGC-1003] – Fixed an issue where the headings for Start and End Date for Initiatives were not displaying on the detail page and fixed an issue where when selecting values for Start and End Date on an existing initiative the save button was not enabled. [IGC-1096] – Fixed an issue where the &amp;lsquo;No Results&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Loading&amp;rsquo; messages were not displaying on the Search Results page when a user performed a search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidance</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/guidance/guidance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/guidance/guidance/</guid>
      <description>When you are viewing the details of an asset, you can click the Guidance () icon to see guidance for adding details to increase the business value of an asset. For example, if you have not assigned an asset or added a sponsor, the following guidance is offered. As you add the suggested details to the asset, the suggestion is removed from the Guidance panel.
In addition to guidance for increasing business value, the guidance displays terms you can add to your Terms glossary based on the content you have entered in certain fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0118/</guid>
      <description>January 2018 January 31, 2018 Bug Fixes  [IGC-887] – Fixed an issue where duplicating a browser tab caused a browser error that prevented a Term page from opening in the new tab by limiting the number of suggested terms to 20 and existing terms to 1000. [IGC-926] – Fixed an issue were when a sponsor contested an asset the color on the “Contested” indicator did not update to gray in the comments panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2019</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0119/</guid>
      <description>January 2019 January 31, 2019 Announcing Entota BackOffice Associates is combining the Cloud and On-Premise Platforms into a new software solution called Entota by BackOffice Associates. In your cloud tenant, you will immediately see the new logo and the name Entota replacing all references to IGC and Information Governance Cloud. The existing features and functionality of your tenant will not be affected by this change. Throughout 2019 and beyond we will continue to introduce new features and improved functionality to Entota that will take advantage of the scale and technologies of the cloud, leverage Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Natural Language Processing, and advanced analytics, allowing us to bring new innovative solutions to the challenges of data migration, quality, governance, and management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0718/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0718/</guid>
      <description>July 2019 July 27, 2018 Enhancement Guidance has been added so that if a user does not have permission to edit an asset, the panel is no longer blank, but tells the user that permission is required. Bug Fixes
 [IGC-1437] – Fixed an issue where a user could not edit a sponsor in IE 11. [IGC-1436] – Fixed an issue where a rule could not be added to a term in IE 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0618/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0618/</guid>
      <description>June 2018 June 21, 2018 Enhancement When defining a Policy using the Quick Add model, you can now access a Rich Text Editor instead of a single text field. You can now format the Policy definition and add links to it.
Bug Fix [IGC-1281] - Fixed an issue where assets could be successfully added with a space in required fields by ensuring that required fields contain text before an asset can be saved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0318/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0318/</guid>
      <description>March 2018 March 26, 2018 Enhancements  Updated the label for the Field count on the System detail page to indicate “Active Fields.” The Field count only includes active fields. Refer to Set Up a System for more information. Fields can now be deleted from a System. Fields that have been deleted from a System appear as Deprecated on the Fields tab of the Data Set detail page. A filter for Depreciated fields has been added to the Data Set detail page on the Fields Tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0518/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0518/</guid>
      <description>May 2018 May 29, 2018 Bug Fix [IGC-1212] – Fixed an issue where users could delete a Vision or Mission by removing the Delete option for those asset types.
May 22, 2018 Enhancement The Entota™ has been enhanced to localize the date format entered or displayed based on the Locale setting in the user’s account. With this enhancement, for existing users the Locale defaults to English, refer to Add a User to learn how to update the default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1118/</guid>
      <description>November 2018 November 16, 2018 New Feature A new Enhanced Search page has been added to the IGC. The Enhanced Search provides an easy way to find and manage assets using the search bar filter, Jump To&amp;hellip; links, and category filters. Category filters can query an asset’s:
 Asset type Endorsement status Assigned users Sponsors The Enhanced Search provides multiple options for accessing strategy and non-strategy assets, and the category filters can help management-level users evaluate assets and their employees’ progress in managing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases1018/</guid>
      <description>October 2018 October 31, 2018 Enhancement A new Migration dashboard has been added. This dashboard provides visibility into progress and status associated with enterprise Data Migration efforts by giving you access to the most important migration project metrics.
Using this dashboard you can:
 Understand the current status of migration waves. Identify any waves that are running behind schedule. Ascertain go-live readiness for a wave. Whether you are responsible for one or multiple waves, across a single instance or multiple instances in the DSP®, you can view progress against milestones to assess risk and determine a need for resource adjustment and communicate effectively to all project stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2018</title>
      <link>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0918/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hcloward.github.io/HCloward.github.io-entota/release-notes/entotareleases0918/</guid>
      <description>September 2018 September 28, 2018 Enhancements The field count on the Systems detail page now updates when a file is uploaded. In previous versions, a browser refresh was required to view the updated field count. Deep Guidance for suggested terms has been added to the Name and Description fields for Systems and Data Sets. Bug Fix
[IGC-1405] — Fixed a performance issue that caused the policy detail page to render slowly in IE 11.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>